/**
 * Created by Austin on 4/6/15.
 */
// factory to hold information that will be shared between the two controllers
// all the questions, choices and correct answers are define and stored here, later to be moved into the database and pulled for each

angular.module('ansFact', [])

    .factory('answerFactory', function() {
        var answer = [];
        var allQuestions = [
            {question:"Where did The Flowerpot Men want to go in 1967?",choices:["New York","San Francisco","Woodstock","Memphis"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"James Bond was searching for what kind of airplace in 'Thunderball'?",choices:["707","Piper Cub","Vulkan","B-52"],correctAnswer:2},
            {question:"Who wrote 'don\'t count your chickens before they are hatched'",choices: ["Aesop","Shakespeare","Ben Franklin","Chaucer"],correctAnswer:0},
            {question:"Which kind of animal did Florence Nightingale often carry around in her pocket?",choices: ["Kitten","Puppy","Owl","Snake"],correctAnswer:2},
            {question:"In which film do the words 'I love you' save the planet earth?", choices: ["The Day After Tomorrow","The 5th Element","Mars Attacks","Independence Day"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"What is the name of the man servant in 'Around the world in 80 days'?", choices:["Pas Partout","Cato","Giles","Machu Picchu"],correctAnswer:0},
            {question:"In which book is there an inn called Admiral Benbow?",choices:["Lords of the Rings","Gulliver\'s Travels","Treasure Island","Peter Pan"],correctAnswer:2},
            {question:"Which actor appeared in the Cranberries music video Ridiculous Thought?",choices:["Bruce Willis","Donald Sutherland","George Clooney","Elijah Wood"],correctAnswer:3},
            {question:"How many earths would fit inside the sun?",choices:["circa 100","circa 1,000,000","circe 10,000","circa 100,000"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"What does a nidoligist study?",choices:["Waves","clouds","Bird Nests","Caves"],correctAnswer:3},
            {question:"What is the more usual name for Roentgen Rays?",choices:["X Rays","Gamma Rays","Ultraviolet Rays","Magnetic Resonance"],correctAnswer:0},
            {question:"A 'Miller' is a move in which sport?",choices:["Ice Hockey","Trampolining","Diving","Chess"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"Festfolk was the original name for which group?",choices:["The Beach Boys","ABBA","Motorhead","Simon and Garfunkel"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"Hypermetropic people are what?",choices:["Obese","underfed","moody","far sighted"],correctAnswer:3},
            {question:"Fredrick Sanger invented which life saver?",choices:["Insulin","Safety Pin","Inflatable Life Raft","Aspirin"],correctAnswer:0},
            {question:"Which NHL hockey team has won the most Stanley Cups?",choices:["Toronto Maple Leafs","Boston Bruins","Montreal Canadiens","New York Rangers"],correctAnswer:2},
            {question: "Herodotus is known as the father of what?",choices:["History","Medicine","Theatre","Music"],correctAnswer:0},
            {question: "The title of which Pink Floyd album is also a chapter in 'The Wind In The Willows'?",choices: ["Wish you were here","The piper at the gates of dawn","Meddle","Animals"],correctAnswer:1},
            {question:"Anemophobia is the fear of what?",choices: ["Spiders","The Dark","Fire","wind"],correctAnswer:3}];
        return{

            // functions created to access and set information between the controllers
            getQuestion: function() {
                return allQuestions;
            },

            getAnswer: function() {
                return answer;
            },
            setAnswer: function(key, value){
                answer.splice(key, 1, value);
            }
        };
    });